Oh, boy.
Hey, Simon Maple here from AI Native Dev.
And I'm here at AI Engineer in San Francisco.
And joining me today is a little puppy, little Sunny AI.
We can actually run around and do the hallway track.
Unfortunately without Sunny, because Sunny has to stay here.
But we're going to talk to people, understand what people are talking about
at the hallway track, what
people are trying to learn at AI Engineer and some of their takeaways.
Unfortunately, this is where we have to part ways.
But let's move on and see who we can chat with.
So it started this week. Harness engineering.
And now loop engineering is the, you know, the dream words.
Is that still the case? I've been out of touch for the last 24 hours.
No, it's definitely the case.
And actually, if you didn't see, in the last 30 minutes, Sonnet 5 dropped.
Okay. What is the major advantage of a loop?
The major advantage of a loop is that the agent doesn't come back to you
and ask for your input every five to tens of operations.
So I think what we've seen is we've seen the models actually
fundamentally change
the way they think about long-running operations. Until very recently,
no matter how much you encourage the agent to continue working,
even if you use, like, emerging features like channels to push notifications
directly into the agent sessions, it would still circle back
and say, I don't know what you want from me, I need your input.
Or here's three choices.
I need you to help me make one of these choices.
Having a proper feedback loop and making sure your agents really understand
what's being done, and also being able to update the memory. What you're doing
today might be really valuable, but in two days that might be something
that's not valuable.
So how is it going to, you know, do the weights and the bias of it?
I gave an early snippet
of what I did this in London, but I built a self-healing Pokémon agent,
and I showed how you can essentially train your code to while playing Pokémon.
I've actually advanced that talk to basically training a model.
Okay, so I've essentially built a Pokémon harness to play Pokémon
that's fine-tuned on an open-weight model.
Don't try this at home. Very expensive, people.
But that's my talk.
I'll have an hour upstairs. Amazing.
Let's see if we can crack it.